Good morning.
Sis, you're here so early.
Is it possible
that I never went home last night?
Oh my god.
How can your body take it?
Have some bread.
I have to say,
you're working too hard.
For this,
I have to criticize Mr. Cheng.
He got off work yesterday
even earlier than Shao.
Mr. Cheng,
you didn't go home either?
What else?
Mr. Cheng, what's wrong
with your face?
Are you allergic to something?
It's nothing.
Just an experiment.
I know who that person is.
It's Lin Rongrong.
She was raped.
Fixative contains a lot of isopropanol.
Inhaling it will depress the central nervous system,
leading to confusion.
The allergic marks on her face
came from this.
This is your analysis.
Tell me what evidence you have.
None at the moment.
But it must be her.
I can go find the evidence.
No need.
I've already found it for you.
At 18:40,
Allen entered the art studio.
He came out in less than ten minutes.
He had absolutely no time to clean up the crime scene.
Look at this video.
Half an hour later,
Lin Rongrong came out of it in a panic.
What does this mean?
I'll summon her immediately for investigation.
No need.
I'll go.
I can help you judge
whether she is lying or not.
Sir.
Please, no.
Mr. Mu.
I'm begging you.
Is anyone home?
Lin Rongrong.
Officer Zhuang, Mr. Cheng.
Hello, Miss Lin.
This is a routine follow-up.
Don't be nervous.
Just relax.
Have a seat.
I'll get you some water.
Okay.
When Mu Weijie died,
you were at the scene, right?
Officer Zhuang,
I don't know what you're talking about.
Then I'll get straight to the point.
When Mu Weijie died,
you weren't just at the scene.
You had sex with him.
And after he died,
you immediately cleaned the scene,
wiping away your fingerprints, skin cells, and bodily fluids, right?
Officer Zhuang,
haven't we already taken the statement before?
I went back right after class that day.
I wasn't in the studio at all.
You were drugged and raped,
weren't you?
Lin Rongrong,
are you still not telling me the truth?
Are you really deciding to live in the shadows for the rest of your life?
I know everything you've been through.
You are a victim.
You don't need to bear all this.
I know it hurts.
We are both women.
Tell me everything you know.
I will try my best to help you.
Trust me.
Trust us.
Why?
Why is it always us who get hurt?
I had already gone home.
But suddenly I had some inspiration,
so I went back to the studio,
wanting to finish the painting I hadn't completed.
Mr. Mu.
Your lecture on Danaë today was really inspiring.
I...
When painting,
don't talk.
Otherwise, you'll ruin its divinity.
Understand?
Mr. Mu,
are you alright?
Mr. Mu.
Mr. Mu, you can't do this.
Don't go.
Mr. Mu!
I'll give you inspiration.
I'll give you inspiration right now.
I'll give you inspiration!
I see.
This Mu Weijie looks like a respectable teacher,
but he actually did such things behind people's backs.
But Lin Rongrong wasn't the killer.
Why would she hide the evidence?
Think about it.
If she had called the police,
wouldn't she become the prime suspect?
So.
Even if she felt physically sick,
she had to try every means to clean up the scene.
From a psychological perspective,
this is called maintaining self-image consistency.
If she admits to being at the scene,
doesn't it mean
the pure label in her self-cognition is broken,
triggering strong cognitive dissonance?
The cover-up behavior is
to complete self-identification by weaving false narratives
and reduce inner pain.
Yeah.
She was unconscious when Allen went in.
So in her mind,
Mu Weijie died because of her.
She didn't want her sexual relationship with Mu Weijie
and his coital death to be exposed.
Coital death?
Let me explain.
Dying during sexual intercourse
is called coital death.
Ximen Qing in 'The Plum in the Golden Vase'
died just like that.
But her attempt to protect her reputation
almost let the real killer get away.
Sis, what are you thinking about?
I was thinking.
You said he might really have been scared to death by Allen.
Why do I find that so hard to believe?
When I went to the crime scene
and saw the victim's body,
I knew that wasn't what happened.
So we still can't do without an autopsy.
Imagine if there was a way
to find the clues inside without an autopsy.
How great would that be?
I know what the clue is.